JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Look who it is.
What an ugly face.
That's beyond fixing, huh?
What are you going to do, Maki-chan?
You can actually tell women
apart by their faces?
I thought you only saw their asses.
I'm asking you what you're going to do.
Now answer me, trash.
You can't use sorcery.
You can't see cursed spirits.
The looks you had
going for you are ruined.
No one'll pay attention to you now.
How sad.
Shall I bully you like I used to?
What are you going to do?
Cling to the shadow of
Okkotsu-kun or Megumi-kun?
Say something, trash.
Maki. Come back.
Have you forgotten?
We're not allowed entry
into the forbidden vault.
The clan head said I could.
Head of the Zen'in Clan?! Me?!
Yeah.
It was in Naobito's will.
No thank you. It'll just be a hassle.
I'm sorry, but please accept it.
Naobito said he would entrust all
of the Zen'in Clan's assets to you.
Both the money and the cursed tools.
If you become head of the clan,
you'll be able to get info on the big
three families and headquarters, too.
It'll make a huge difference in
what we can do from here on.
Then you do it, Maki-san.
You can have it.
No one would accept me right now,
and they wouldn't follow me.
The fact that you possess
the hereditary technique,
the fact that you can
activate your Domain,
and the attention you received from Satoru
creates a hand that
barely wins you acceptance.
Their acceptance?
Does it even matter what the
members of the Zen'in Clan think?
You'd get all those benefits if you
became the head, wouldn't you?
It can't be me yet.
I wouldn't be able to
create a place for Mai.
All right.
Come back here!
Why?!
Why must you always be like this?!
Just once, make me happy
I gave birth to you, Maki.
Father!
You should've said something if you
were planning this from the get-go.
You just jumped the gun.
Though it's true Megumi Fushiguro
would be better than you.
Huh?!
There are more than a few
voices pushing for him
as an opportunity to repair
relations with the Gojo Clan.
Though you know there's no way we
could accept Megumi Fushiguro
being entrusted with all the assets.
Then why were you dilly-dallying?
Because in addition to the Gojo Clan,
Megumi Fushiguro has built an
effective relationship with the next head
of the Kamo Clan, Noritoshi Kamo.
If we eliminated him without cause,
it would only put our
Zen'in Clan in a worse position.
With Gojo Satoru sealed
and the power balance between clans
shifting, we would fall behind.
I get all that, so why now?
You haven't really read the notices
from headquarters, have you?
Satoru Gojo has been deemed an accomplice
in the Shibuya Incident and is
hereby expelled from Jujutsu Society.
In addition, any attempt to free him
from his seal will be deemed a crime.
We can make use of that.
We'll execute Megumi Fushiguro,
Maki, and Mai,
as traitors plotting to
release Satoru Gojo.
Killing his own daughters
sure adds believability.
Yeah. With this, the trust headquarters
places in us will grow firmer.
Is old man Ogi okay with that, though?
Ogi came up with this plan.
There are no cursed tools here, Maki.
We emptied it out in anticipation
of your intentions.
Why did you come here, idiot?
Juzo Kumiya's Masterpiece,
The Cursed Tool "Dragon Bone"
Secret Art: Falling Blossom Emotion
Do you know
why the previous head of the clan was my
older brother, Naobito, instead of me?
Because you're an asshole who'd
murder his own children, right?
Why was I passed over for clan head?
How?!
It was because you two, my children...
I know I broke...
...were such defective failures!
...his blade!
You broke my blade
and judged that my reach
had been shortened,
so you closed in.
This is why you're hopeless.
I'm not a swordsman. I'm a sorcerer.
Trying to gauge me by the
standards of such a failure
is absolutely ridiculous!
I'll say it as many times as I must.
I wasn't chosen to be the
previous head of the clan
because of you two!
My older brother's technique
had a shallow history,
and its potential to be inherited or
not wasn't a big point of contention.
As a jujutsu sorcerer,
I never lagged behind my brother
in any area except one:
the quality of my children!
Children must never drag
their parents down!
Didn't you know?
Dragging each other down is considered
a virtue in this country.
This room is used for
training and punishment.
We keep countless grade 2 and
lower cursed spirits in here.
They're frightened by me right now,
but soon enough, they'll crawl
out to devour you two.
A Heavenly Pact?
Enhanced physical prowess?
What of it?
We sorcerers train every day,
and we further strengthen our bodies
with cursed energy in combat.
Maki,
the power you possess is something
that every single one of us has.
Good riddance,
the sole stain on my life.
You certainly... are tough.
I always figured it would
come to this one day.
This sucks.
You basically know at this point
what my technique can do, right?
But I can't create anything
large or complicated.
I'm wounded from where he cut me, too,
so once I create this, I'll die.
Later.
Good luck on your own after this.
Hey! Mai!
Wait!
What are you talking about?!
Just come back here!
I've known for a long time now
why twins are considered
inauspicious by jujutsu sorcerers.
You have to offer something
in order to gain anything.
This goes beyond just pacts.
The fact that we go through pain to
grow stronger follows the same logic.
But that balance never functions properly
in the case of twins like us.
Because jujutsu views identical
twins as the same individual.
Get it?
You are me, and I am you.
You can long to grow stronger
and work so hard you spit up blood,
but it's all pointless.
Because I don't want to
grow stronger at all.
Even if you don't have any techniques,
it's pointless if I have one.
So long as I exist, Maki,
you'll always be incomplete.
I get it!
Just come back!
This is all I'll leave you with.
Cast off the rest.
I'll take all the cursed energy
and everything else with me.
Just promise me one thing.
Destroy it all.
All of it, you hear,
Big Sis?
Mai! Mai!
Mai!
Wake up!
Wake up...
Mai!
Mai...
Wake up...
The cursed spirits were exorcised?!
What?!
My body remembers.
I worked so hard to forget that fear...
Technique Release - Blazing Courage!
Technique Release - Blazing Courage
Very well!
This time, I'll burn you down to the
marrow of your bones with my own hands!
Come at me, fail—
Mai, I'll get started.
Episode 51
Perfect Preparation
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Why's it so noisy?
Jinichi-san!
Maki's lost her mind!
She murdered Ogi-san!
The Kukuru Unit is already
trying to deal with her!
I guess even Ogi
can be caught off-guard if he's attacked
in his sleep or while on the toilet.
Capture her before I get there.
Yes, sir!
If we dawdle too much,
then as your captain, I'll be the
one Jinichi acts smug toward.
Oh, don't kill her.
Kukuru Unit Captain, Nobuaki Zen'in
I'll finish her off myself.
The Kukuru Unit.
Are you listening?
The young men of the Zen'in Clan
who don't possess techniques
Yes, sir!
Move it, move it!
are obligated to join the Unit,
and the martial arts are drilled
into them day and night
so they can serve under the Hei.
There she is! In the Ton room!
What are you going to do?
I wonder what I wanted to do.
Visual confirmation of two
unidentified cursed tools!
Maki had also been a member
until she joined Jujutsu High.
Why wouldn't you stay at
the bottom with me?
You were right.
Surround her! Surround her!
I'm sure that would have been
the right choice for us.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mai.
Get her!
Just promise me one thing.
Destroy it all.
All of it, you hear?
Hey, how's it coming along?
She went for the jackpot.
Chojuro-san's technique?!
The Hei are here!
The Hei.
"Hei"
They are composed of those
whose abilities are recognized
as semi-grade 1 or higher by
Jujutsu High's standards.
They're the Zen'in Clan's strongest
collection of sorcerers.
How is she still moving after
taking Chojuro-san's attack?!
She's fast!
She easily broke through
my guard of cursed energy!
Is she really the same Maki?!
Jinichi-san!
Keep holding her there, Ranta!
I...
I can't keep holding her!
Forget about me, Jinichi-san!
The current Zen'in Clan only exists
thanks to the whim of Toji-san!
You must have realized it!
Maki is now the same as that man!
Do it here!
And now!
Kill her!
You did it, Jinichi-san.
How cruel.
Head of the Hei, Naoya Zen'in
Have you no heart?
Nah. She took it with her.
Everyone says I'm a genius.
I'm going to be the head
of the clan after my father.
I heard there's a loser
in the Zen'in Clan.
They say the man ain't got
a smidgen of cursed energy.
He must be real depressed.
I wonder what kind of
pathetic look he's got!
Three, four, five, nine, ten, eleven.
You!
You...
ain't Toji-kun!
The sin of the insignificant
is the ignorance of strength.
No one was able to understand Toji-kun.
Save maybe Satoru-kun.
You ain't the one!
The one to stand among them... is me!
Projection Sorcery can't be
used to create movements
This is bad.
that excessively ignore
physics and trajectories.
Six, seven, eight, thirteen, fourteen.
Likewise, there's a limit to
how much acceleration
can be added to one's
speed upon activation.
Conversely, the longer the technique
is continuously activated,
the further one can raise their speed.
The one to stand among them... is me!
I won't stop now!
I won't screw up like I did back then!
Force is weight times speed!
She wants a head-on fight, huh?
I'll give you a hug.
I'll punch through her at top speed!
While Projection Sorcery is active,
anything the user touches with their palm
must create a movement
within 1/24 of a second.
If they fail,
they're frozen for one second.
She was probably planning to take
my attack and stop my movement,
even if it broke her ribs.
Like I'd fall for such obvious bait!
You really are an impostor!
Twenty-four times, right?
You and and old man Naobito
aren't just fast.
There's something off to it.
You were creating 24 motions per second.
I can finally see it after
obtaining this body.
You im—
...po—
Sorry.
Say that again?
Mother?
No! Stay back!
Mother. Please, listen.
Why?! Why must you...
Why did you tell me to come back then?
Huh?
Wh-What are you talking about?
No...
No!
No! No!
Stupid bitch failed to end me!
Are you shitting me?!
I can't focus my cursed energy!
Damn gutter trash!
I'm glad I gave birth to you.
Mai-chan!
This is why...
I told you not to go!
Please take care of her.
What are you going to do now, Maki-chan?
The six members of the Hei,
the nine members of the Akashi,
and the 21 members of the Kukuru Unit
who were absent from the Zen'in Clan's
home that day all met untimely deaths.
At present, no residuals have
been detected,
and autopsies revealed faint traces of
cursed energy in the corpses' wounds
that are believed to come from the
cursed tool used as the murder weapon.
Several days later,
both the Gojo Clan and Kamo Clan
motioned for headquarters
to remove the Zen'in Clan
from the big three families.
Headquarters has tabled this motion.
Hakari-san was expelled for
clashing with the upper brass.
A fight club?
You do not talk about the fight club.
I can't get close.
Itadori, you snoop around from the inside.
I love it when you're hot, Kin-chan.
Want to get high on my passion?
Next Episode
Passion